[music]
[音乐]
Hello and welcome to section 3
您好，欢迎来到第3节
of lesson 3.
第三课
In this part we are going to talk about how to avoid,
在这一部分中，我们将讨论如何避免，
wherever possible, the use of forEach method.
尽可能使用forEach方法。
Now
现在
the problem that we have is that as Java programmers,
我们面临的问题是，作为Java程序员，
we think imperatively. That means that we tend to think
我们必须思考。这意味着我们倾向于思考
in terms of loops for repetitive behaviour. That's what we used to: We use
就重复行为的循环而言。那就是我们过去的习惯：
while loops, we use for loops,
while循环，我们使用for循环，
and so on. we're also very used to using variables
等等。我们也很习惯使用变量
to hold state. So that's the thing we're used to,
保持状态。这就是我们习惯的事情
but the problem is that sometimes we can try and still apply this behaviour
但问题是有时我们可以尝试仍然应用此行为
when using streams, because there are things we can do, which
使用流时，因为有些事情我们可以做，
enable us to use this kind of approach but it's
使我们能够使用这种方法，但是
not the right way to do things. This is wrong and we need to avoid it
不是正确的做事方式。这是错误的，我们需要避免
in order to use streams correctly. Let's
为了正确使用流。让我们
have a look at an example then where I've written some code and I'm still
看一个例子，然后我写了一些代码，我仍然
thinking imperatively. I'm still thinking in the way that
认真思考。我还在想
I would write Java before. What I have
我以前会写Java。我有的
is collection of transactions, and
是交易的集合，并且
from that I want to add up all the values
从那我想把所有的值加起来
of those transactions and create a total. To do that
这些交易并创建总计。要做到这一点
I thought, right I'm going to use forEach method
我以为我会使用forEach方法
because I'm going to take my collection of transactions, create a stream source
因为我要收集交易记录，所以创建一个流源
and then for each element on that I want to get the value
然后对于每个要获取的值
and add it to my total. To do that
并将其添加到我的总数中要做到这一点
I thought very clever and I'll use this LongAdder class,
我以为很聪明，我将使用此LongAdder类，
which is new in JDK 8 and is designed
这是JDK 8中的新增函数，旨在
for streams. It's also designed for multiple threads
用于流。它还设计用于多线程
that are executing to update values. It's designed
正在执行以更新值。它是设计的
for frequent updates and infrequent reads.
用于频繁更新和不频繁读取。
What I've got here, then, is using a Lambda expression
那么，我在这里使用的是Lambda表达式
to add the current value of
添加的当前值
the transaction to my total. This is problematic because when
交易总额。这是有问题的，因为当
modifying state,
修改状态
which is the wrong way to do things in a functional approach.
用函数方法做事是错误的方法。
And then we've got
然后我们有
the sum. If you want take the correct functional approach
总和。如果您想采取正确的函数方法
then we need to do this kind of thing.
那么我们需要做这种事情。
We take the transaction collection
我们接受交易收集
and we generate stream source from that. We then parse that
然后我们从中生成流源。然后我们解析
to mapToLong. mapToLong
来mapToLong。 mapToLong
uses a Lambda expression, which in this case
使用Lambda表达式，在这种情况下
will convert the transaction
将转换交易
object on the input stream into a long value,
输入流上的对象变成一个long值，
which is the value of the transaction. So our
这是交易的价值。所以我们
output stream  is going to be stream of long values. We passed that to sum
输出流将是长值流。我们通过了总结
and sum is, in effect, a reduction, which will create a single result, which is the
总和实际上是减少，将产生一个单一结果，即
total
总
all the transactions in our collection. This
我们集合中的所有交易。这个
is a functional approach. We're not modifying state, not even trying to
是一种实用的方法。我们不修改状态，甚至不尝试
apply imperative style of coding to it
对它应用命令式的编码样式
or create explicit loops. There are
或创建显式循环。有
legitimate places to use forEach. We saw that in last
每个地方都可以使用的合法场所。我们最后看到了
part of the lesson, where we talk about infinite streams. But
本课的一部分，我们讨论无限流。但
if we want to do something like this; we want to take our transactions in
如果我们想做这样的事情；我们想接受我们的交易
this case we want to print out lines of all the clients.
在这种情况下，我们要打印出所有客户端的行。
This is a perfectly legitimate use of forEach. We take our
这是对forEach的完全合法使用。我们把我们的
stream source, pass each of those elements to forEach and
流源，将每个元素传递给forEach和
we consume it by printing out the name of the client.
我们通过打印客户端名称来使用它。
We can make this parallel if we want, so we could create a parallel stream,
我们可以根据需要进行并行处理，因此可以创建并行流，
but obviously, in that case, we wouldn't be concerned by order.
但是显然，在那种情况下，我们不会为订单感到担心。
Because using a parallel stream we would get
因为使用并行流，我们将获得
non-deterministic behavior because of the way the threads
由于线程的方式而导致的不确定行为
execute. But it is quite legitimate to use
执行。但这是很合法的
forEach in certain situations. To summarise section 3 then,
forEach在某些情况下。总结一下第3节，
if you're thinking of using the forEach method
如果您正在考虑使用forEach方法
when you're constructing a stream piece of code then
当您构建流代码段时
stop. What you need to do is consider,
停。您需要考虑的是
before you actually use forEach, could it be replaced
在实际使用forEach之前，可以将其替换吗
by combination over map and
通过地图和
reduction? If you can,
减少？如果你可以的话，
then you should because it's much more likely that,
那么您应该因为它更有可能，
in order to be functional you need to use that map
为了发挥作用，您需要使用该地图
followed by the reduction rather than forEach. But,
其次是减少而不是每次减少。但，
if you're doing something like printing values from a stream
如果您正在执行类似从流中打印值的操作
then it can't be replaced by map and a reduction, so it is quite
那么它就不能被map和归约替换，所以它相当
valid. If you're just consuming the value on the input stream,
有效。如果您只是在使用输入流中的值，
then forEach can be quite valid and that is the end
那么forEach可能是非常有效的，到此为止
of this part of the lesson.
这部分课程的内容